const week4Data = [
  {
    question:
      "In “AID”, a set of sensor nodes are deployed over an agricultural field.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Ultrasonic sensor senses the distance at which an object is located.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In case of static sensors, where to deploy and/or activate sensors in WSN is a coverage problem.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Objective of coverage in WSN is to use maximum number of sensors and minimize network lifetime.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A crossing is covered if it is in the interior of at least one node’s coverage disk.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is/are correct for stationary wireless sensor networks.",
    options: [
      "Topology cannot be changed automatically.",
      "Node failure may result in partition of networks.",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "Most problems in static WSN can be classified as -",
    options: [
      "No coverage",
      "More coverage",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is/are correct with respect to UAV networks?",
    options: [
      "Multi-tasking",
      "Large coverage area",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "UAV networks are scalable.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "In Mobile WSN, the Data Mules",
    options: [
      "Collect the data from sensor nodes",
      "Goes to the sink and delivers the collected data",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "Neither (a) nor (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question: "The full form of AUV is -",
    options: [
      "Antenna Used Vehicle",
      "Autonomous Underwater Vehicle",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "Neither (a) nor (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Autonomous Underwater Vehicle",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Humans carry their devices and move around. Sensors embedded within the devices record readings. Sensory readings are then transmitted for processing. This paradigm of sensing is known as –",
    options: [
      "Machine Centric Sensing",
      "Device Centric Sensing",
      "Human Centric Sensing",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Human Centric Sensing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Energy of Devices and Participant selection are not two major problems in Human Centric Sensing.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following network topologies is used in UAV networks?",
    options: ["Bus", "Star", "Both (a) and (b)", "Neither (a) nor (b)"],
    answer: "Star",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The M2M Application Platform provides integrated services based on device collected data-sets.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
];
